{
  "lecture2": [
    {
      "question": "Outline of Acts",
      "answer": "Acts Outline:<ul><li>1:1–8:1 — Church in Jerusalem</li><li>8:2–12:25 — Church in Judea, Samaria, and Antioch</li><li>13:1–14:28 — 1st Missionary Journey (NE Med)</li><li>15:1–35 — Jerusalem Council</li><li>15:36–18:22 — 2nd Missionary Journey</li><li>18:22–21:16 — 3rd Missionary Journey</li><li>21:17–28:31 — Jerusalem to Rome</li></ul>",
      "type": "outline"
    }
  ],
  "lecture4": [
    {
      "question": "In which chapter is the Pentecost event found?",
      "answer": "Acts 2",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture5": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Salvation is found in no one else”",
      "answer": "Acts 4",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture6": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “We must obey God rather than men”",
      "answer": "Acts 5",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Choosing of the seven deacons",
      "answer": "Acts 6",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Stoning of Stephen",
      "answer": "Acts 7",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture7": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Philip and the Ethiopian",
      "answer": "Acts 8",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Three chapters of Saul's conversion",
      "answer": "Acts 9, 22, 26",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Peter’s first food vision",
      "answer": "Acts 10",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture8": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Jerusalem Council",
      "answer": "Acts 15",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Believe in the Lord Jesus Christ and you will be saved”",
      "answer": "Acts 16",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Paul's Areopagus speech",
      "answer": "Acts 17",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture9": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Apollos first appears",
      "answer": "18",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Paul and disciples of John the Baptist",
      "answer": "Acts 19",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture10": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “the whole counsel of God”",
      "answer": "Acts 20",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “For two whole years Paul stayed there in his own rented house ... and boldly and without hindrance preached the Kingdom of God.”",
      "answer": "Acts 28",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture11": [
    {
      "question": "Outline of Romans",
      "answer": "Romans Outline:<ul><li>1:1-7 — Opening</li><li>1:8-15 — Thanksgiving and Travel Plans</li><li>1:16-17 — Theme</li><li>1:18-5:21 — Justification</li><li>6-8 — Sanctification</li><li>9-11 — Israel - Has God's Word Failed?</li><li>12:1-15:13 — Hortatory</li><li>15:14-33 — Travel Plans</li><li>16 — Greetings and Closing</li></ul>",
      "type": "outline"
    }
  ],
  "lecture12": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “I am not ashamed of the gospel”",
      "answer": "Romans 1",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “the wrath of God is being revealed ... and men are without excuse.”",
      "answer": "Romans 1",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture13": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Gentiles ... show the requirements of the law written on their hearts”",
      "answer": "Romans 2",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “there is none righteous, no not one.”",
      "answer": "Romans 3",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture14": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God and are justified freely by his grace.”",
      "answer": "Romans 3",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture15": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Abraham believed God...”",
      "answer": "Romans 4",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: Adam / Christ comparison",
      "answer": "Romans 5",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture16": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “the wages of sin are death, but the gift...”",
      "answer": "Romans 6",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “the law is spiritual but I am fleshly”",
      "answer": "Romans 7",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “all things work together for good”",
      "answer": "Romans 8",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ],
  "lecture17": [
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “It is not as though God’s word has failed”",
      "answer": "Romans 9",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Did not know Righteousness of God and sought to establish their own”",
      "answer": "Romans 10",
      "type": "chapter"
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the chapter: “Christ is the end of the law.”",
      "answer": "Romans 10",
      "type": "chapter"
    }
  ]
}
